# Vraj Devganiya

Part-time Student

#### Contact

**Address** 

North York, ON, M3J 1K6

Phone

+1 437 263 6707

E-mail

vrajdevganiya6707@gmail.c om

## **Skills**

Customer service and assistance

Excellent

Stocking

Very Good

Operating cash register

Excellent

Cleaning procedures

Excellent

Shelving of products

Excellent

Enthusiastic Gas Station Attendant with a friendly nature and excellent relationship with customers. Dedicated to comprehensively enhancing customer experiences through helpfulness and maintaining a clean workspace. Successful at restocking quickly and assisting customers. I am willing to take on any task to help organization's mission succeed. Fast worker with attention to detail and completeness.

# **Work History**

#### 2022-07 -Current

#### **Gas Station Attendant**

Petro Canada, Toronto, ON

- Maintained clean and orderly work station.
- Offered assistance to customers unfamiliar with fueling vehicles, demonstrating appropriate measures for pumping gas.
- Processed fuel and merchandise transactions by operating POS system with accuracy.
- Built trustful relationships with customers to encourage return visits.
- Maintained inventory of all saleable items.
- Responded to customer requests efficiently and with knowledgeable assistance.

#### 2020-03 -2022-10

#### Cashier

D-MART, Surat, Gujarat

- Helped customers complete purchases, locate items and join reward programs.
- Operated cash register for cash, check and credit card transactions with excellent accuracy levels.
- Provided friendly service and assistance to clients promote customer loyalty, satisfaction and sales.
- Worked flexible schedule and extra shifts to meet business needs.

### 2021-10 -2022-03

#### **IELTS Tutor**

Kanan International, Surat, Gujarat

- Maintained excellent attendance record, consistently arriving to work on time.
- Conducted student progress reviews and provided individual feedback for each student on strengths and weaknesses.
- Multitasked and prioritized student assignments to meet strict deadlines and last-minute requests.
- Instructed 56 students in listening, speaking and academic reading and writing.

#### **Education**

2022-05 -Current

# Advanced Diploma: Computer Programming And Analysis

Seneca College of Applied Arts And Technology -North York, ON